Larry Harmon zine collection LSC.2376
UCLA Library Special Collections
Larry Harmon zine collection
1984-2024
UCLA Library Special Collections
LSC.2376
10.8 linear feet (28 boxes)
Larry Harmon started the independent Genetic Disorder zine in 1987. Harmon's zine included detailed researching and reporting of the odd tales of Southern California. Harmon participated in the Kill Zinesters Summer Vacation Tour of 1996 with Darby Romeo of Ben Is Dead and Noel Tolentino of Bunnyhop among other zinesters. The Larry Harmon zine collection ranges from 1984-2018 and contains Harmon's collection of zines, including issues of his own zine Genetic Disorder.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
COLLECTION CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIO MATERIALS: Materials will require assessment and may need further processing for safe access. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Larry and JoAnna Harmon, 2018.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9993537073606533
Biographical / Historical
Larry Harmon started the independent Genetic Disorder zine in 1987. Harmon's zine included detailed researching and reporting of the odd tales of Southern California. Harmon participated in the Kill Zinesters Summer Vacation Tour of 1996 with Darby Romeo of Ben Is Dead and Noel Tolentino of Bunnyhop among other zinesters.
Sources:
Christopher, Roy. "Genetic Disorder". Level, July 3, 2009. https://levelmag.com/shorts/genetic-disorder-zine.
Whiting, Ben. "The Zine Scene / Indie publishers of alternative periodicals hit the road to increase their visibility." SFGate, June 30, 1996. https://www.sfgate.com/entertainment/article/The-Zine-Scene-Indie-publishers-of-alternative-2976798.php.
Scope and Contents
The Larry Harmon zine collection ranges from 1984-2018 and contains Harmon's collection of zines, including issues of his own zine Genetic Disorder.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged alphabetically by the title of the zine and chronologically within titles.
Related Materials
Darby Romeo Collection of Zines (Collection 1746). Available at UCLA Library Special Collections, Charles E. Young Research Library, UCLA.
Punk culture -- California -- 20th century; Punk rock music; Zines
- 10 Things Jesus Wants You to Know - #16, Seattle, WA, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 2600 - V.10, #4 - Middle Island, NY, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 2600 - V. 14, #2 - Middle Island, NY, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 312 - #4, Chicago, Illinois, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- 360 Degrees - #3, San Diego, California, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 360 Degrees - #7, San Diego, CA, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 360 Degrees - #8. San Diego, CA, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 360 Degrees - #14, San Diego, CA, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- 949 Market - San Francisco, CA, 2002 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Aaron from Probe correspondence, 1996 (Box 27, Folder 1)
- Action Girl Guide - #1, Staten Island, NY, 1993 - 1994 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Asylum For Shut-Ins - #1, Bedford, OH, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Audio Vomit - Gainesville, FL, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Attention Deficit Disorder - #10, Tampa, FL, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- And the Survey Says!!! - #1, Los Angeles, CA, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- a quest for things to do - #7, San Francisco, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- The Amigo - #6, Chula Vista, CA, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- All the Answers - #3, Phoenix, AZ, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- All the Answers - #4, Phoenix, AZ, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Almost Nothing but Record (and Tape) Reviews - Vol 1, #7, New York City, NY, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Almost Nothing but Record (and Tape) Reviews - Vol 2, #2, New York City, NY, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Almost Nothing but Record (Tape & Video) Reviews - Spring/Summer issue, New York City, NY, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Almost Nothing but Record (Tape & Video) Reviews - Fall issue. New York City, NY, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Amped by Jon Resh, 2001 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Angry Thoreauan - #1, Anaheim, CA, Oct-Nov 1991 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Angry Thoreauan - #2, Anaheim, CA, Jan-Feb 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Angry Thoreauan - #3, Anaheim, CA, June - July 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Angry Thoreauan - #4, Anaheim, CA, Nov - Dec 1992 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Angry Thoreauan - #5, Anaheim, CA, Feb - March 1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Angry Thoreauan - #6, Anaheim, CA, July 1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Angry Thoreauan - #7, Anaheim, CA, October 1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Angry Thoreauan - #8, Anaheim, CA, January - February 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Angry Thoreauan - #9, Anaheim, CA, April 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Angry Thoreauan - #10, Anaheim, CA, August 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Angry Thoreauan - #11, Anaheim, CA, November 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Angry Thoreauan - #17, Anaheim, CA, July 1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Angry Thoreauan - #23, Hollywood, CA, December 1998 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Answer Me! - #2, Hollywood, CA, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Answer Me! - #3, Hollywood, CA, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Answer Me! - #4, Portland, Oregon, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- The Assassin and the Whiner - #10, Los Angeles, CA, March 1998 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- The Assassin and the Whiner - #11, Los Angeles, CA, January 1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- The Assassin and the Winter - #12, Los Angeles, CA, March 1999 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- The Assassin and the Whiner - #13, Los Angeles, CA, February 2000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- The Assassin and the Whiner - #14, Los Angeles, CA, June 2000 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Babysue - Vol. 3, #4 - Decatur, GA, Spring 1996 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Babysue - Vol. 4, #1, Decatur, GA, Summer 1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Babysue - Vol. 4, #3, Decatur, GA, Spring 1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Babysue - Vol. 4, #4 - Decatur, GA, Spring 1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Babysue - Vol. 5, #1, Decatur, GA, Summer 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Backfire - Vol. 5, #1, Seattle, WA, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Badazz Mofo - Vol. 2, #3, Portland, OR, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Bald Cactuz - #14, Leeds, England, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- bAnal Probe - #4, Austin, TX, September 1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Band Promotional Photographs (Box 26, Folders 1 - 6)
- Beer Frame - #7, Brooklyn, NY, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Burn Collector - #12, Carrboro, NC, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Beer Zine - Los Angeles, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Besmirched - #4, Vista, CA, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Big Bang Fanzine - #1, Anaheim, CA, 1996 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Blow My Colon - #2, Claremont. CA, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- bobby is fred - #2, Los Angeles, CA, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Boredom - Berkeley, CA, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Bottom Drawer Zine - #2, Thousand Oaks, CA, Undated (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Boy, Does High School Ever Suck - #12, Santa Rosa, CA, Fall 1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Boing Boing - #12, San Francisco, CA, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Bruce on a Stick - #3, Tarrytown, NY, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Bruce on a Stick - #4, Tarrytown, NY, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Bunnyhop - #5, San Francisco, CA, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Burnt Offering Funzine - #2, Huntington Beach, CA, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Butt Ugly - #6, Waukesha, WI, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Buzz Kill - #3, Phoenix, AZ, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Barracuda - #8, Los Angeles, CA, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Barracuda - #20, Los Angeles, 2004 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Beer Can Fanzine - #1, Portland, OR, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Beer Can Fanzine - #2, Portland, OR, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Beer Can Fanzine - #3, Portland, OR, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Beer Can Fanzine - #4, Portland, OR, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Black Market - #5, San Diego, CA, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Black Market - #8, San Diego, CA, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Black Market - #9, San Diego, CA, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Black Market - #10, San Diego, CA, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Black Market - #11, San Diego, CA, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Black Market - #13, San Diego, CA, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Blue Fire Hereafter Zine, 2000 (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Blue Persuasion - #1, Lexington, KY, December, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Blue Persuasion - #2, Lexington, KY, March, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Blue Persuasion - #3, Lexington, KY, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Blue Persuasion - #4, Lexington, KY, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- The Worst of.... Boiled Angel - #1-8. Bensenville, IL, 1988 - 1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- The Book of False Gods - #1, Schenectady, NY, November 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- The Book of False Gods - #2, Schenectady, NY, February 1992 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- The Book of False Gods - #3, Schenectady, NY, August 1993 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Book Your Own Fuckin' Life - #1, Minneapolis. MN, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Book Your Own Fuckin' Life - #2, Minneapolis, MN, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Book Your Own Fuckin' Life - #3, Minneapolis, MN, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Book Your Own Fuckin' Life - #4, Minneapolis, MN, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Book Your Own Fuckin' Life - #8, Minneapolis, MN, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Book Your Own Fuckin' Life - #9, Minneapolis, MN, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Cactus Pricks - #4, Tempe, AZ, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Caboose - #3, Chicago, IL, December 2002 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Casazone - #1, Spring Valley, CA, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Chunklet - #17, Athens, Georgia, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Complexificationstrategory - Portland, OR, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Crank - #4, Philadelphia, PA, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Crinkle/Hiss - #1, San Francisco, CA, 1996 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Calico - #5, Brockton, MA, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Calico - #6, Brockton, MA, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Calico - #7, Brockton, MA, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Calico - #8, Brockton, MA, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Carbon 14 - #8, Philadelphia, PA, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Carbon 14 - #9, Philadelphia, PA, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Carbon 14 - #29, Philadelphia, PA, 2006 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Carbon 14 - #30, Philadelphia, PA, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Carbon 14 - #31, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- ChinMusic - Vol. 1, #1, San Francisco, CA, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- ChinMusic - #4, San Francisco, CA, 2000 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Chinmusic - #6, San Francisco, CA, 2003 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- ChinMusic - #5, San Francisco, CA, 2002 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Chip's Closet Cleaner - #11, Washington, DC, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Chip's Closet Cleaner - #13, Washington, DC, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- D.E.S - #3, Seattle, WA, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
- The Duplex Planet - #129, Jamaica Plain, MA, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Dear Jesus - #39, New York City, NY, Spring 1992 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Dirt Culture - #4, Las Cruces, NM, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Dirt Culture - #5, Las Cruces, NM, 2001 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Dishwasher - #7 / #8, Arcata, CA, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Dishwasher - #9, Arcata, CA, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Dishwasher - #10, Arcata, CA, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Dishwasher - #11, Arcata, CA, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Dishwasher - #12, Arcata, CA, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Dishwasher - #13, Arcata, CA, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Dishwasher - #14, Arcata, CA, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Dishwasher - #15, Arcata, CA, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
- The Dissimilars + The Kassos 7'' Vinyl, 1999 - 2005 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  CONTAINS UNPROCESSED AUDIOMATERIALS: Audio materials are not currently available for access and will require further processing and assessment. If you have questions about this material please email AskLSC@library.ucla.edu.
  This folder contains three 7-inch vinyl records. Landmine, It Would Be My Pleasure To Fuck You Up, and Jimmy's Room.
- Dregs - #5, Liverpool, UK, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 1)
- Dropout - #2, Portland, OR, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Dropout - #3, Portland, OR, 2007 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Drenched - #4, Honolulu, HI, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Echoline - #1, San Francisco, CA, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Enquirer - #1, San Diego. CA, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Error - #102, Richmond, VA, 1995 (Box 25, Folder 2)
- Evil - #5, Chicago, Illinois, September 1993 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Everything I Touch Turns To Shit & Garbage - #1, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Elk - #12, Brooklyn, NY, July 2006 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Ear of Corn - #15, Stow, OH, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Ear of Corn - #17, Stow, OH, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Ear of Corn - #20, Stow, OH, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Ear of Corn - #21, Stow, OH, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Ear of Corn - #24, Stow, OH, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Ear of Corn - #25, Stow, OH, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Ear of Corn - #27, Stow, OH, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Ear of Corn - #28, Stow, OH, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- El Zine de Eugene - #6, Miami, FL, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- El Zine de Eugene - #7, Miami, FL, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- El Zine de Eugene - #8, Miami, FL, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- El Zine de Eugene - #9. Miami, FL, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- El Zine de Eugene - #10, Miami, FL (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Excursion - #6, Seattle, WA, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- The Fanzine That-Had-No-Name - Vol. 2, #11, Santa Barbara, CA, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Fungus Boy - #9.5, Ottawa, KS, 2003 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Full Force Arkopolis - #3, New Orleans, LA, Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Fat Kid Fanzine #1 / Spiderworks #2 - Austin, TX, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Flesh and Bones - #8, Middlesex, NJ, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Future Sex - #5, San Francisco, CA, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Future Sex - #6, San Francisco, CA, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Future Sex - #7, San Francisco, CA, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Food Geek - #5, Los Angeles, CA, 2001 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- FYF Quarterly - Los Angeles, CA, 2011 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Factsheet Five - #32, Rensselaer, NY, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Factsheet Five - #33, Rensselaer, NY, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Factsheet Five - #34, Rensselaer, NY, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Factsheet Five - #37, Rensselaer, NY, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Factsheet Five - #38, Rensselaer, NY, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Factsheet Five - #39, Rensselaer, NY, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Factsheet Five - #40, Rensselaer, NY, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Factsheet Five - #43, Rensselaer, NY, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Factsheet Five - #45, Atlanta, GA, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Factsheet Five - #46, San Francisco, CA, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Factsheet Five - #47, San Francisco, CA, 1992 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Factsheet Five - #48, San Francisco, CA, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Factsheet Five - #49, San Francisco, CA, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Factsheet Five - #50, San Francisco, CA, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Factsheet Five - #51, San Francisco, CA, 1993 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Factsheet Five - #52, San Francisco, CA, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Factsheet Five - #53, San Francisco, CA, 1994 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Factsheet Five - #55, San Francisco, CA, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Factsheet Five - #56, San Francisco, CA, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Factsheet Five - #57, San Francisco, 1995 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Factsheet Five - #58, San Francisco, CA, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Factsheet Five - #59, San Francisco, CA, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Factsheet Five - #60, San Francisco, CA, 1996 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Factsheet Five - #61, San Francisco, CA, 1997 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Factsheet Five - #63, San Francisco, CA, 1998 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Feminist Baseball - #12, Seattle, WA, Winter 93/94 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Feminist Baseball - #13, San Francisco, CA, Summer/Fall 1994 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Fine Print Distributors Catalog, 1996 - 1997 (Box 27, Folder 3)
- Fiz - #2, Los Angeles, CA, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Fiz - #3, Los Angeles, CA, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Fiz - #4, Los Angeles, CA, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Fiz - #5, Los Angeles, CA, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Fiz - #6, Los Angeles, CA, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Fiz - #8, Los Angeles, CA, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Fiz - #10, Los Angeles, CA, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Fiz - #9, Los Angeles, CA, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Fiz - #11, Los Angeles, CA, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Fiz - #12, Los Angeles, CA, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Fiz - #13, Seattle, WA, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Fizz - #1, Seattle, WA, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Fizz - #2, Seattle, WA, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Fizz - #4, Seattle, WA, 1995 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Fizz - #6, Seattle, WA, 1996 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Fizz - #9, Seattle, WA, 1997 (Box 28, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #68, Whittier, CA, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Flipside - #71, Whittier, CA, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Flipside - #72, Whittier, CA, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Flipside - #73, Whittier, CA, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Flipside - #74, Pasadena, CA, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #75, Pasadena, CA, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #76, Pasadena, CA, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #77, Pasadena, CA, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #78, Pasadena, CA, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #80, Pasadena, CA, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #81, Pasadena, CA, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #82, Pasadena, CA, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #83, Pasadena, CA, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #84, Pasadena, CA, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #85, Pasadena, CA, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #87, Pasadena, CA, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #88, Pasadena, CA, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #89, Pasadena, CA, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #90, Pasadena, CA, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #91, Pasadena, CA, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #94, Pasadena, CA, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #95, Pasadena CA, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #96, Pasadena, CA, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #97. Pasadena, CA, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #98, Pasadena, CA, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #104, Pasadena, CA, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #105, Pasadena, CA, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #111, Pasadena, CA, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #115, Pasadena, CA, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #116, Pasadena, CA, 1998 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Flipside - #122, Pasadena, CA, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Flyers + Single Sheets, 1990s - 2000s (Box 27, Folder 4)
- From the Diane Files - #1, Cleveland Heights, OH, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Fucktooth - #14, Cleveland, OH, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Fucktooth - #19, Cleveland, OH, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Fucktooth - #20, Cleveland, OH, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Fucktooth - #21. Cleveland, OH, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Girlyhead - Vol. 1, #1, San Francisco, CA, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Gods Dogs - Seattle, WA, 1986 - 1993 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Gogglebox - #1, New York City, NY, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Gogglebox - #3, New York City, NY, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Gogglebox - #4, New York City, NY, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Greedy Bastard - #12, Yonkers, NY, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Gearhead - #2, San Francisco, CA, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Gearhead - #3, San Francisco, CA, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Gearhead - #10, San Francisco, CA, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Gearhead - #11, San Francisco, CA, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Genetic Disorder - #8, San Diego, CA, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Genetic Disorder (GD is Dead) - #9, San Diego, CA, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Genetic Disorder - #10, San Diego, CA, 1993 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Genetic Disorder - #11, San Diego, CA, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Genetic Disorder - #12, San Diego, CA, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Genetic Disorder - #13, San Diego, CA, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Genetic Disorder - #14, San Diego, CA, 1996 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Genetic Disorder - #15, San Diego, CA, 1997 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Genetic Disorder - #16, San Diego, CA, 2002 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Genetic Disorder #16 Poster - San Diego, CA (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Genetic Disorder - #17, San Diego, CA, 2003 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Genetic Disorder - #19, San Diego, 2009 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Genetic Disorder Catalog - San Diego, CA, 1997 (Box 25, Folder 8)
- Genetic Disorder Ephemera, 90s - 2000s (Box 25, Folder 7)
- Get Loose - #4, Palatka, FL, Undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Get Loose - #5, Palatka, FL, Undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Goat - #1, Spring Valley, CA, October 1992 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Goat - #2, Spring Valley, CA, December 1992 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Goat - #3, Spring Valley, CA, January 1993 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Goat - #4, Spring Valley, CA, February 1993 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Goat - #5, Spring Valley, CA, September 1994 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Grand Royal - #1, Los Angeles, CA, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Grand Royal - #2, Los Angeles, CA, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Great God Pan - #10, Hermosa Beach, CA, 1997 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Great God Pan - #11, Hermosa Beach, CA, 1998 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Grind - #3, Mesa, AZ, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Grind - #4, Mesa, AZ, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Grind - #5, Mesa, AZ, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Hamburger Eyes, February 14, 2001 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Highball Magazine - Vol. 1, #1, Los Angeles, CA, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Hit List - Vol. 1, #1, Berkeley, CA, February/March 1999 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- House of Pain - #10, Nashville, TN, August 1993 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- The Hungover Gourmet - #6, Lutherville, MD, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Hatewagon - #1, Tuscon, AZ, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Hatewagon - #2, Tuscon, AZ, 1992 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Hatewagon - #3, Tuscon, AZ, 1993 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Heartattack - #2, Goleta, CA, June 1994 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Heartattack - #4, Goleta, CA, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Heartattack - #11, Goleta, CA, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Heartattack - #13, Goleta, CA, 1996 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Heartattack - #28, Goleta, CA, 2000 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Heartattack - #35, Goleta, CA, 2002 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Heartattack - #41, Goleta, CA, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- High Heels Slut - #9, Belgium, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- High Heels Slut - #10, Belgium, 2007 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- High Heels Slut - #11, Belgium, 2010 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Hippy Core Fanzine - #2, Mesa, AZ, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Hippy Core Fanzine - #4, Mesa, AZ, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Hippy Core Fanzine - #5, Mesa, AZ, 1988 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Hippy Core Fanzine - #6, Mesa, AZ, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Hippy Core Fanzine - #7, Mesa, AZ, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Horizontal Action - #10, Chicago, IL, 2002 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Horizontal Action - #11, Chicago, IL, 2003 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Horizontal Action - #14, Chicago, IL, 2004 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Idiosyncracy - #2, Los Angeles, CA, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- The Illusion of Progress - Fredonia, NY, 2005 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- The Imp - Chicago, IL, 1998 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Interbang Fanzine - #6, Ravenna, OH, 1997 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Insight - #2, Kalamazoo, MI, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Instruction Manual - Valencia, CA, Undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
- I'm Johnny and I Don't Give a Fuck - #4, Vancouver, Canada, Undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
- I'm Johnny and I Don't Give a Fuck - #5, Vancouver, Canada, 2024 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Jersey Beat - #40, Weehawken, NJ, Spring 1990 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Jersey Beat - #43, Weehawken, NJ, Summer 1991 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Jersey Beat - #45, Weehawken, NJ, Winter 1992 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Jersey Beat - #46, Weehawken, NJ, Summer 1992 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Jersey Beat - #47, Weehawken, NJ, Fall 1992 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Jersey Beat - #48, Weehawken, NJ, Winter 1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Jersey Beat - #51, Weehawken, NJ, Summer 1994 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Jersey Beat - #52, Weehawken, NJ, Fall/Winter 1994 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Jersey Beat - #58, Weehawken, NJ, Fall 1996 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Jersey Beat - #64, Weehawken, NJ, Winter 1999 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Jersey Beat - #68, Weehawken, NJ, Fall/Winter 2000 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Jersey Beat - #72, Weehawken, NJ, Fall/Winter 2002 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Juxtapoz - V.4, #1, San Francisco, CA, Winter 1997 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Pool Dust - #30, Tempe, AZ, August 2004 (Box 13, Folder 2)